One girl transforms, now bright, kind, and cheerful, but someone else changes too, into something dark, fierce, and cruel.
One girl transforms, now bright, kind, and cheerful, but someone else changes too.
I'm sorry, did it happen again?
Did what happen?
Nothing, my apologies. Lately I've been having these blackout moments where my mind goes blank.
It goes blank, as in...
It's nothing to worry about, I'm probably anemic or something.
Anyway, I guess you read your note, the one I left on your desk?
Uh, yeah, are you still free on Saturday?
Oh, sorry, there's somewhere I have to be.
Kurumi, you can stop hiding now.
You know me too well.
Crazy, huh?
This really does make it a lot harder to understand why origami turned inverse, wouldn't you say?
Yeah, but this origami was able to accept the death of her parents.
I don't get it. What happened?
Let me see if I've got this straight.
So you're saying, this world exists because you used Kurumi's time travel powers,
and you did that to save origami's parents who should have died five years ago,
and the purpose of that was to avoid what she would have turned into.
Yeah, that's the gist of it.
Hmm, fascinating.
I think now I get why you've been acting a little strange for the last day or so.
It's true. Maybe origami shouldn't have inversed in this world.
Regardless, she definitely did, and now we have devil to contend with.
I've analyzed her encounter with Shin on the roof.
He's telling the truth.
Believe it or not, origami Tobiichi hasn't the faintest idea that she's a spirit.
But how can that be?
Shin, you managed to change the course of time.
So you and Kurumi are the only ones with actual knowledge of the original world, correct?
Yeah.
And as for Kurumi, considering her own powers are what brought this about, she's kind of an exception.
So if I had to guess from everything you've told me, in order to retain knowledge of the original world,
two conditions must be met.
Being directly hit by Kurumi's yudbet, and having spirit powers flowing through oneself.
With both conditions met, it's possible that one's memory of the original world may be recovered.
We know that origami was shot by Kurumi's yudbet, so the first condition was met.
Separately, she's ended up living a peaceful life thanks to Shido's interference.
But then, when phantom showed up on the scene and gave her spirit powers...
She finally remembered everything.
However, as a self-defense mechanism, her memories were split in two.
Essentially, there's one origami who lives in peace, and then there's the spirit hunter, devil.
So now, as soon as origami senses spirit power, she loses control of her mind and memory.
And then, the inverse version of her is awakened.
The theory works and is consistent with what we know.
The question is, what can we do about it?
As long as origami's a spirit, there's only one thing for Rattata Skirt to do.
Make her fall for me, right?
Correct.
That's how we'll seal her spirit powers.
You'll need to convince origami to go out on a date with you.
Think you can handle that, lover boy?
What now? Is there a problem?
Nothing. It's just...
Huh? You've already promised to meet up with her this Saturday?
So you hit on her before even knowing that she was a spirit?
The heck?
Dude.
Well, I mean, it's complicated.
I can't believe I wrote him a note.
Since when did I become some kind of lovesick girly girl?
I don't know.
Maybe it's...
It's from him!
Okay. Got a reply.
Yes, thank you. That time and date will work for me.
Is that too impersonal?
Dear Itsuka, as I write this, the winds of autumn fill me with hope and anticipation.
And the moon sits like a big egg in the sky as I wonder how you're faring tonight.
Who says that? No one!
I really appreciate you inviting me here today, Itsuka.
You okay?
Yeah, my pleasure.
Since we're hanging out, could we maybe do first names now, pretty please?
Oh, of course we can.
Sounds good.
That's more like the origami, I know.
Sorry, too fast?
Guess I'm just anxious to say your name.
I mean, cause it's so pretty.
Thank you.
I've always been glad my parents picked it for me.
If you like calling me that so much, say it as often as you want.
I don't mind at all.
Feel free to call me Shido, too.
Thanks. I'll work up the courage soon.
Kill me now. This is unbearable.
So, what do you think we should do today?
Good question.
Here we go.
Your choices, everyone.
Mm-hmm. That seems right to me.
I hated to pass up the first choice, but going someplace where they can't talk is a pretty classic blunder.
Plus, choice number two is a safe and versatile option.
Even if she isn't into shopping, they'll have lots of fun.
All right, Shido. We're ready. Go with you.
Hold up a sec.
I want to test out a different choice.
Oh, yeah!
Emotional levels are unstable.
Origami Tobiichi is distraught.
Big shocker there?
What are you thinking, Shido?
Talk your way out of it!
Right. I will.
Sorry about that. Wrong building.
Oh, so that wasn't it.
Okay.
Man, I genuinely thought Origami would go crazy for that.
You never cease to amaze me.
Look, just go with two, okay?
Take the girls shopping.
Roger.
Break it gently. How's her happiness level?
I hope it didn't drop too drastically.
Yeah, about that.
Her emotions are bouncing all over the place,
but her happiness actually seems to be rising.
Are you serious?
Hey, where are we going to go shopping?
Um, let's see.
Your choices, everyone.
It's got to be the third one.
Huh?
Have you lost your damn mind?
No way can you take a girl there on the first date.
Yeah, but Origami and Everdegex go together like peanut butter and jelly.
Wait, you know what I'm saying, right?
Origami, this way.
Here we are.
What do you think?
I'm so sorry, Itsuka, but I have to admit,
I don't even know what most of the stuff in here is.
Yeah, right? Very funny.
Then what's all that?
Huh?
What? What's going on?
Why do I have all this?
I don't understand what's the matter with me.
What made me pick up those things?
Don't worry about it.
It's totally my fault for taking you to the store in the first place.
How would you feel about a new outfit as my way of apologizing?
That sound good?
What? No, I can't let you do that.
Please don't worry, I got it.
In exchange, all I ask is that you let me be the first to see you wearing it.
That's the only payment I need.
Tell me something.
Are you kind of a ladies' man?
You're almost too good at this.
No!
No, it's not true at all!
Then I guess I'll take you up on that offer.
And while I'm at it, I should make sure it's an outfit that you'll like a whole lot.
You ladies' man.
She really called you out, didn't she?
Yeah, not helpful.
Shut up.
Hey, I don't remember saying it was a bad thing.
Shin, Origami just went into a dressing room in the back of the store.
Don't lose sight of her.
Right, thanks.
Origami!
Are you okay?
I...
What am I doing?
Sorry.
I'm coming in!
No, please don't!
So, let me ask.
Did you pick this because you thought for some reason that I'd be into it?
I don't know!
That's why I freaked out!
I mean, I don't even remember taking these clothes off the rack!
I'm sorry.
Again.
For some reason, I'm weird today.
Don't let it bother you.
Nothing you've said or done has fazed me.
Thanks for that.
Sorry, bathroom break.
I'll be right back.
Sure, go ahead.
Oh.
So sorry to keep you waiting like that.
Hey.
What you doing?
No.
Wait.
This isn't whatever you're thinking right now.
Your spoon fell off the table, so I was just picking it up.
I'm so sorry.
It's nothing.
Don't sweat it.
It'll dry in no time.
What are you doing?
Why am I...
You have to believe me.
It's like my body's moving all on its own.
What is going on with me?
Oh.
Origami Tobiichi's emotional levels have now stabilized.
Her happiness meter still remains high.
The mood isn't bad either.
With any luck, we could wrap this up in one day.
Perhaps.
However, it seems clear that she remains anxious about something.
It could just be basic nerves regarding whether Shin will accept her or not.
I'm not surprised after all she did.
I feel like it should only take one more push, though.
Seriously?
So, you mean you're done with the AST, then?
My anemia and those blackout moments are both pretty solid reasons to quit.
Also, I just don't know anymore.
Is it really the right thing to do?
Continuing to wipe out spirits the way that I have?
Forgive me.
I forgot it was a spirit that was responsible for the death of your brother, too.
You don't have to be sorry for that.
Listen, I think you're very smart to question it, and I completely agree with you.
And to be totally honest, my brother would say the same thing.
Oh, my sweet friend.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you for telling me that.
Happiness meter climbing!
Maximum value has been reached!
Hmm.
That must have been the source of her earlier anxiety.
So now it seems she's turned a corner.
Shido!
It's looking good!
I'd say it's time for you to dive in for the kill!
We're coming!
Are you all right?
You hurt?
No.
Shido, I'm...
Origami, are you okay?
You okay?
Spirit...
No, her spirit power.
Shido, get out of there!
Origami?
What was that?
What's that?
What am I sensing?
Shiver.
My heart is restless.
There, look!
What are you thinking?
It's too dangerous!
Origami is after me now!
Our only chance to steal her is to do it while her armor is incomplete!
If I run away, the city will be demolished.
I can't let her...
Not again.
Never again!
Shido, stay back!
Hydrofolium!
We should be able to use Fraxinus' main battery to break her spirit barrier for three seconds.
You'll have to use that chance to get close and steal her...
No, Kodori, run!
Kodori!
Please, no.
Not again.
Origami!
Toka!
You all right, Shido?
We're here to help!
You guys...
Shido, fill us in.
Who the heck is that?
I sense a dreadful spirit power.
You're right.
That's Origami.
The transfer student?
It's far too dangerous to fight her.
I should probably tell you all to run away.
But I am begging you to help me save her anyway.
Well, isn't that obvious?
After all, you're the one who saved me.
You're the one who made my world possible.
So this time, it's finally my turn to help you.
Thank you, everyone.
Wait for me, Origami.
Where am I?
Did I lose...
Consciousness again?
I thought I was just with Itsuka.
Are you...
Me?
I don't get it.
What is this?
Oh, my gosh.
Are these...
My memories?
We'll distract her, Tio.
Go!
Suggestion.
Get out while you can.
That's it.
Great job, you two.
We call Gabriel.
Gabriel!
Rondo!
And march!
What the heck, Matsumi?
Why do you have to be such a copycat?
I've just always wanted to try that.
Here we go!
At this rate, he can't even get close to her.
Huh?
Shida, you've got to reach her!
Thank you!
Shiriyan!
Yoshida!
Ah!
Now's your chance! Move!
Go save the transfer students!
You guys are the best!
We're incoming!
No! Let me in there!
Let me in!
Open your heart!
We're incoming!
You're looking at the one who killed your mom and dad.
It's not true! That never happened in this world!
Because Itsuka's brother...
Now, Itsuka saved them.
And what about my memories, huh?
Do you think I can ever take back the truth that I killed them?
But that's...
I am you, and you are me.
And even if the world's remade, the memories will remain, always.
There's no hope in the world for me now.
And that means, you too.
Stop! Enough!
Please, just stop!
I can't... I can't do this!
Please...
Somebody...
Somebody please help me!
Origami!
Can you hear me?
Itsuka?
What the...
What is Shiro doing here?
Don't carry this burden on your own!
Like I told you five years ago,
You're not alone!
I'm always here for you!
All of your sadness and your hate!
Let me carry all of it for you!
If you're lost, I'll find you!
When something happens and it's too much,
Please come to me!
Give it all to me!
Everything!
It's okay!
I'll take all of it!
Do you hear me?
Okay?
Don't let despair take you over, Origami!
No matter how many worlds you try to break,
I'll fight to get to you!
I know you're in despair!
I'll never stop trying to help you save yourself!
Shiro...
My friend...
Come on!
Reach out to me, will ya?
I won't lose you!
Origami!
I...
Thank you, Shiro.
If you hadn't been here for me,
I would have ended up doing something else
I'd never be able to take back.
The fact that I killed my mom and dad
is never going to go away from me.
Nor will the sin of slaying the ones I did
in the original world.
That will stay with me forever.
Even if...
If it's changed so that it never even happened.
Origami...
You're right.
Unfortunately, I think that's a burden
you'll always have to bear.
I feel like I need to apologize.
The feelings I've had towards you weren't actually love.
I got two feelings confused, I think.
I felt I could rely on you.
But now I realize that when I lost my parents,
I had no other choice but to cling to you.
Well, I'm honored.
But it took bravery to trust me.
So you're saved because of you.
Shiro...
Oh, yeah.
I've got something of yours.
And I need to give it back.
I held more than tears.
Wouldn't you say?
Shiro, do we...
Oh!
Good grief, man.
We'll never learn our limits.
Or so I hope.
Good morning, Shiro.
Morning, Origami.
Here, I have something to wipe your tears with.
Thank you.
What?
Origami, what are you doing?
School swimsuit.
It retains moisture well.
Oh, I picked these up for you, too.
Okay, I'm a little confused
because when all that happened,
didn't you say you never loved me to begin with?
Yeah, which means our real love story
can start now.
You better stay away from Shiro!
Get off him!
Yes!
Yuck!
Hey!
Yes!
Ooh!
Hey!
Say what!